Today I will show you how to make a real Christmas set.
In this model, we will use a new feature called Glow2025.
It will explain our real-time editor and version generator.
In the top one, we will show you how to make different needles.
We will show you how to make a hollow needle.
We will also show you how to make a thick needle.
We will also show you how to make a needle without a gap.
We will also show you how to tie a string.
Let's take a look at the editor.
We will create a basic round loop.
Then we will modify it.
Now let's open the library window.
Then we will create a new library.
In this material folder,
we can get all the materials we used in the past.
Here we have some materials and some accessories.
First, we will import the ZPRJ file.
Then we will import the ZPRJ file.
This file will be downloaded in Connect shopping.
In our official account, we have uploaded a lot of free basic formats.
We can use it.
We can choose free and then choose the official account.
You can select gender.
There are many different styles here,
I use this model, it is a V1 model
You can click here to join the shopping cart
After the display is added to the shopping cart
Deliver orders in our shopping cart
It can show that it has been successfully purchased
If we want to use it, we can drag it in directly for use
Now it's ready for you
No need to download
Let's change the style now
Now let's take a look at this style
First of all, we have to make a turned collar
Then the sleeve also has to be turned up
Then
And
It is added to the bottom of it
A small box side
And make a drawstring
First of all, let's deal with the body
First delete the excess curve points
Because our normal sweater style
Some sweater styles
It is all
Straight-line
There is not too much curve
Now we will
The front piece of
The first length is shortened
To shorten it to 80
Click to confirm
The back piece is the same
Adjust it a little bit straighter
The back piece is also
Turn up and down
Then adjust its size
Then push it by pulling the lever
Turn up or down
And pull it out
Then the back piece is adjusted
Try to make it a little straighter
The back piece is also the same
Then push it to the inside
And you can see it
Right click
Also enter the movement distance as 10
The back piece is also the same operation
So
is the same operation. When entering, then we come to adjust this curve point,
delete the excess curve point, and adjust its curve line to be smooth.
Next, let's adjust its bottom plate. In the close window, lift it up a little first,
then modify it, and then lengthen it. When you lengthen it, you can enter its overall width with the right key.
Here I entered a 1430, click OK. We will rearrange this plate again.
Open the arrangement point on the model, and arrange it on the model's waist, and then modify it again.
This time, I'm going to adjust its height, and you can see that the height has changed.
The width of the center is also reduced, and the width can be adjusted.
Then I will remove the curve point on the model's waist.
And this time I will remove the curve point on the model's waist.
Next, I will remove the curve point on the model's waist.
Then I will close the nozzle of the model's waist.
And I will also remove the curve point on the model's waist.
Treat it as a straight-line shape
Put it inside on both sides
The angle is about 90 degrees
Then we pull this sleeve down by 50
Is to make this whole sleeve longer and wider by 5 cm
Next, we click on the outside of the board
Right click, click on the outside of the board
Select the expansion of the outside of the board
Here, select extension
The extension diameter is 190
Hook it up to the inner line
Then click OK
The distance of the fold of the sleeve is extended
Next, we choose the folding arrangement tool
Fold it out
Then use the sewing line
Sew the two sides together
Simulate
Then pull a little and adjust
Harden a little and then simulate
Make it more flat
Next, let's make the little lotus leaf edge of this sleeve
Use the folding arrangement tool
Let's make one
Width is 780
Height is 23 mm
A folding arrangement of 23 mm
Then we use the line sewing tool
Sew it to the sleeve
You can freeze it
Then add it to the outside
Simulate
This kind of small foldable plate
We can adjust its particle diameter
A little bit smaller
Now it is adjusted to a 10
Then we control D
Copy it to match
Let's simulate
Dissolve
Simulate
Okay, next we continue to make
This shoulder
A decorative board
Still
First, draw a inner line on it
Press the Ctrl key
To draw a curve you want
Double click to end
Then use the adjustment curve tool
Adjust its shape
Adjust it to a curve you want
It is possible to make a curve
We can make it smaller
Set the length to an angle
Adjust the width to a certain width
And press the Ctrl key
Then you can make a curve
A purplish curve
Make it smaller
Adjust until it is the curve you want
Then slightly simulate
It's ok
to make a wide 600 mm, a 75 mm high
shape. This side still uses the thread sewing tool to sew to the sleeves.
You can also freeze it and put it outside.
Pull it a little.
Then we sew the two ends together.
We right-click on this line and add an internal line border.
This is 30.
Let's cut and sew again.
Let's simulate again.
Select these two panels, Ctrl D, and still copy it and align it to the sleeve on the other side.
Then we deal with the collar.
Delete the original collar first.
Then modify its collar line.
Use the panel outline expansion.
Here we choose a shrink.
For the shoulder strap, we will use the shoulder strap.
We set one with a impact of 25.
Click and confirm.
Now the collar is outwards 25 mm.
The back panels are the same.
The collar is wider, a little wider.
The sleeve also solidified.
We modify the decorative panels on both sides.
Also modify it.
Next, let's make a folded collar.
First, let's use the measurement tool to measure the neck width of the model.
The neck width is about 300 mm, which is 30 cm.
Next, let's make a half-shape of the collar.
Let's enter 160 cm.
This is to give the collar a loose amount of 20 cm.
The height is 180 cm. Click OK.
Move the collar out a little bit.
Then right-click and select the edit line.
Then place the collar on the neck of the model.
Before the simulation, let's first freeze the collar.
Then let's sew it.
Use the measurement tool.
Then let's sew the collar, the front and the back of the collar.
Sew the collar on both sides.
Use the measurement tool.
Then let's draw the inner line of the folded collar.
Right-click to find the inner line of the collar.
Enter 67 mm here. Click OK.
Then use the folding arrangement tool to fold it outward.
Then fold it outward.
Now let's simulate.
The back of the hair is a little stuck, so let's reverse-activate this hair.
Select reverse-activate virtual model.
Then let's simulate it again.
Then right-click and select the shape to solidify.
Then let's turn down the volume a little bit.
After we have optimized the shape,
we will simulate it again, and it will not transform.
Now let's freeze it.
Then let's make some structures on the front side of the collar.
Right-click and select the internal line border.
The border is 25.
The expansion number is 2.
Click to confirm.
The back piece is also the same operation.
The internal line border.
Click to confirm.
Then we choose these two internal lines.
Cut and sew.
The back piece is also the same.
To make it easier for everyone to see,
we have now adjusted it to a random color.
Let's simulate it again.
Then let's take a look again.
Now we need to make a decorative line on this board.
We use the plus point division tool.
Select the average segment.
The number of lines is 4.
Click to confirm.
Then we still use the plus point division tool.
Lift it up a little bit.
In this position, we add a point.
In the back position, we also add a point.
In the middle part, it is still an average segment.
Here, the average is divided into 3.
Click to confirm.
Use the internal line tool.
Then we draw a fold line here according to the points we just drew.
Double click to end.
Double click to end in the middle.
Pay attention to the chopped off points.
And now you can see that there's a little now.
Ei, et cetera.
And now it's just fine.
Draw a line in the middle of it
So its diameter is 2.5
Change the number of curves to 1 and click OK
Then we sew it to the board
Then to the outside
This thin and small board is still a little smaller than the diameter of its diameter
This side is 5 and the thickness of the gap is 1
Then slightly hardening
If it is still not very stable
Then we can also adjust its diameter to be a little smaller
This side is changed to a 3
Then we
Ctrl D
Copy and paste
Hardening
Simulate
Sew the two ends together
Simulate again
Okay, next we will make this tie drawstring
We use this internal line
We use this internal line on the front panel to draw a internal line of 160 cm long
Click OK
Then we select this line and copy it
Then enter its diameter
When copying, you can enter its diameter by right-clicking
Then enter a 25
Then select these two internal lines
Then copy it again
Then when pasting, right-click
This diameter I said is 75
Click OK
We select the transverse fold tool
Select the transverse fold tool
Then select the reverse direction
Click OK
The back is the same as the front and back are the same
Then copy the transverse fold tool
Use the internal multilinear line tool
Draw a internal line of 180 mm at the back
Click OK
Then copy this line
And copy this line
Click OK
Then copy this line
Then enter 20 in the header and click OK.
Select these two lines and copy them.
When pasting, right-click.
Enter 48 in the header and click OK.
The same is the same tool.
Select and click OK.
Before sewing, we first harden the two panels,
and then simulate it to make it fold naturally.
This way, it is not easy to penetrate after sewing.
Now we use the line sewing tool
to sew the fold of the back piece.
Simulate it.
Then we come to the front piece.
For the front piece, let's make a wide 30,
with a height of 110.
Click OK.
This panel is a support type panel.
We use the free sewing tool.
Then sew it to the two sides of the front,
0 degrees, on these two internal lines.
Add to the side.
And then simulate it.
Ctrl D, copy and match.
You can slightly move it down a little bit.
This way, it just fits in the position of its waist.
For this panel,
we need to add a transparent panel to it.
So let's add a fabric.
Then name it transparent panel.
Change its opacity to 1.
Then apply these two panels to the fabric.
You can see that this panel
becomes transparent.
It becomes transparent.
Unseal the hardening, and simulate it.
Change the diagonal of this plate from 0 to 10.
change the diagonal of this plate from 0 to 10.
You can now start adding new lines.
Perfect!
This is how you makebons on a panel.
You don't need to even add detail here.
Just do it one time.
Just do it balance the panels.
Then from the bottom to the top, let's enter a distance of 15 from this current 1 and click OK.
In the middle, the average segment is 3, 3 points, click OK.
The other side is also the same operation.
Now let's use the round-shaped board tool to create a round-shaped board with a diameter of 14.
Click OK.
Change the diameter to 3.
Change the movement thickness to 1.
Then use the same method.
Use the round-shaped tool in the middle.
Click OK.
Enter 8 directly and click OK.
Then use the inner line tool to draw a line in the middle and then cut it off.
Delete the other half.
This is our metal ring with a band.
Metal ring board.
Now we know the first small board.
Then we use the free sewing tool to sew it up according to the points just added.
Put it on the outside.
It's a bit of a thread now, so let's pull it out.
Because there are some folds here, it's easier to thread it in.
Then we put it on the outside.
Put it on the outside.
Then we use the inner multilinear line tool.
Then we draw a short inner line.
The length of this inner line is 5.
Let's copy.
Several metal ring boards.
There are four on one side.
Then we paste the other half in a mirror.
Okay, let's adjust its position, and move it to the other side, and put it in a close position to simulate it.
Let's adjust its position a little bit.
Let's print this big body board.
Then activate the middle board,
to make it more flat.
Then we create a small body board with a width of 30cm and a height of 5mm using the shape board tool.
This is our first tie board.
Now we sew it to the metal ring board,
and put it in this position.
Then we sew it to the metal ring board, and put it in this position.
Then we sew it to the metal ring board,
and put it in this position.
Stick them together by rooting,
then put them inside like this.
Okay, then we will copy it. After copying, lengthen it to 40 and click OK.
Because this plate is a diagonal, so let's lengthen it a little bit.
Arrange the position for it.
Then sew it to the corresponding metal ring plate.
Then let's change its coordinates.
Change the coordinates to screen coordinates.
Okay, the simulation is complete.
Then let's copy the next plate.
Then move the positioning ball to place it in its position.
Pay attention to its back and forth.
And the order of its sewing.
Let's simulate it.
Okay, there is no problem with the sewing.
Then we continue to copy and paste.
Repeat the previous step.
Then we continue to sew it.
drag it to the corresponding position
and simulate it.
Here you need to change the sewing line
and pull it back
Then it is here
to change this sewing line
and simulate it.
That's right.
OK, let's continue to copy
this piece of board.
Ctrl C, Ctrl V
We can also directly
in the 3D window
do the sewing
so that it is easier to see
its sequence
the sequence of sewing
Copy this piece of board
move it to
a position behind
and sew it
It should sew this one
OK, simulate it.
Finally,
let's copy the first one
this small tape
adjust its sequence
and interlocking relationship
This one needs to be used
to adjust the grid tool
to pull it out
Use the selection grid
comparison tool
and then pull it out
OK
Check to see
if there is any problem
In this way,
let's see
We can make a column
with a pattern
and the pattern
It can be adjusted
according to the pattern
For example,
let's say
the pattern in the top
is the pattern of the column
and the pattern in the bottom
is an inner line
We can also use
the pattern in the bottom
to sew a butterfly knot
to make it hard
Then,
we can use
the inner line tool
to draw a 5 cm
inner line
here
5 mm
inner line
In this drawing body,
you can see that
Let's find the butterfly knot in the library and click OK.
Move it to the closest position.
The butterfly knot is relatively wide, so select all the pieces of the butterfly knot and freeze them.
Then freeze the small piece of the butterfly knot in the middle.
Then shrink the main part of the butterfly knot.
Then the small piece of the butterfly knot in the middle is also narrowed.
Let them come close to the width of the string.
Then we can sew them directly in 3D printing.
Simulate.
Then the butterfly knot is sewn.
Unlock.
You can also continue to freeze here.
There is a little fight here, so this side also needs to be backfired.
Then it will stabilize like this.
First, unhook the butterfly knot.
Then select these pieces of the tie and Ctrl D.
Copy it to match.
Let's freeze the main part of the butterfly knot first.
Then simulate it again.
This piece of the butterfly knot is also backfired.
Hide.
Unlock the main part of the butterfly knot and simulate it again.
Check the structure of the butterfly knot.
Slightly adjust its penetrating situation.
The metal ring plate is also hardened.
This plate can also be used to select the grid tool.
Pull it out.
Select the grid comparison tool.
Pull out.
OK.
Basically OK.
Then we select the internal line of this metal ring plate.
Then right-click to select the cut-and-sew.
The other side is the same.
Select these internal lines and cut-and-sew.
We take it out.
The small panels inside are set to transparent panels.
And these small panels are also transparent panels.
Then we build a new metal ring fabric.
Apply the metal ring fabric to these small half-circle panels.
Then set it to a metal material.
Put it on the table.
The color is also set to gold.
Let's hide this print.
You can see its effect.
We have finished the current style.
Next, let's use our paper printer to make the structure of this needle.
This kind of clothing has a total of six needle fabrics.
There is a large body.
Then the bottom, the sleeve, and the collar.
There is also a sleeve decoration strip.
Now, we first add a fabric to it.
Name it large body.
Then add the bottom fabric.
The bottom fabric.
Then the hollow.
The hollow.
The hollow fabric of the collar.
Name it hollow.
The hollow chest.
Then the fourth one is the sleeve.
The fifth one is the collar.
Then the sixth one is the sleeve.
The fourth one is the sleeve.
Then the fifth one is the sleeve.
This is a kind of clothes that sits around the top.
This is tension-resistant.
Finally, it will go onto the whole table.
The last one is a sleeve.
Select the wool product on the type side, select the needle method, and select the flat needle.
In the 3D window, you can directly see the structure of the needle.
If you don't see it, or it's flat, then we find the wool product on the clothing rendering type side.
Click on it to see this structure.
In the previous version, you can directly adjust the direction of the wool.
In the version of 2025.2, there is a small wool ball in the back.
Click on it directly to open the piece editor.
This is our piece editor.
On the top, there is a button to open the piece editor.
In the previous version, you can directly adjust the structure of the piece.
You can adjust the length of the thread, the width of the thread, and the thickness of the thread.
You can also adjust the density of the thread.
The length of the thread is the number of threads in the loop of the piece.
Now let's modify these numbers.
The length of the thread is 8.
The horizontal number of threads is 8.
Adjust the density of the thread to 2mm.
Click on the reverse crochet button again.
You can see the effect of the change.
Adjust the density of the thread to 4.
The depth of the curve and the thickness of the sand line can be adjusted and changed based on our value changes.
Click on the triangle below the depth of the curve.
Here is the total number of inches per inch, the number of rows per inch, and the thickness of the surface.
There is a moving small icon in front.
If this icon is gray, it means that this value will be calculated by the depth of the curve, and it is an automatic measurement result.
If we click on it, we can automatically enter the number of inches per inch, the number of rows per inch, the number of rows per inch, and the thickness of the surface.
We can automatically enter them.
Now, if we adjust it, we can also see that the thickness of the surface is the same as the actual changes.
Now, let's select it.
Then, let's redo the piece.
In the window below us,
we will see that the tip width is changed.
Then we can move it by adjusting the width according to your wishes.
I am just adjusting the width, today we can adjust the width as our last moment.
In this video, I have hope it畫 a little more than enough space.
What do you want to change the13 d cutting angle.
We can see how many degrees it is in theved.
the full view of this piece of paper, then we have to choose the zoom to the full view, and it
is also like a 3D window. As you can see, you can use the shortcut key of the small number key on the keyboard to
preset the angle and preset the operation for it. Then, let's take a look at the side.
On the left side, the menu on the right side is its kind of needlework. There are four options, including front needlework, which is
our default needlework now, and back needlework. When we use it, we choose it, and then press the left button to drag it, and we can change this needlework.
This side is also the same operation. Press it to drag it directly, press the simulation button, and it can apply the shrink effect of this needlework.
Then let's take a look at the front needlework, the front loop needle, and the back loop needle.
Then let's take a look at the front needlework, the front loop needle, and then press the slow button to Report vähän, press the time button to Это
offers you some directions to push the hands from the right side, press the handle, then the
upper side.
Then, it turns up so quickly.
is to make two holes.
Then we choose the backstitch,
and make a backstitch effect on both sides.
This stitch method is like a hollow little heart.
Then let's simulate it again.
You can see that the shrink effect is different depending on the change of the stitch method.
Then let's take a look at the above display type.
The first one is the default thick gusset line.
The thick gusset line is actually the one that shows
the shape of our piece of paper.
The thin gusset line shows the structure of the gusset.
The random color gusset line is made up of different colors of gusset.
It is convenient for us to check the structure of the gusset line.
Now we apply this gusset to our 3D clothing.
We can see that the gusset line shows the shape of the gusset.
The gusset line shows the shape of the gusset.
Click on Apply.
Then you can see that the structure of the gusset line is applied to our 3D window.
Click on Add and Close,
close the window.
Then let's adjust the basic color.
The color is red.
Click OK.
Then we continue to do the bottom plate, and the piece structure of the bottom plate is also used in the sleeve, and in the gap of the shoulder.
So we choose these parts, then select the wool product, select the needle, and then click on this to open the piece editor.
The number here is still 8, and the number of horizontal number circles is also 8.
The width of the gusset line is set to 1.5 here, and the density of the circle is set to 5.5.
Click on this to redo the piece.
Then on this piece of paper,
we will first put this back needle,
and then first give it a grid to make a piece of design, click on the simulation.
Then we use this front bed fabric to make a small hollow structure for it,
then simulate, look at its shrink effect,
then use the back bed fabric.
Then we use this back bed fabric to make a small hollow structure for it, look at its shrink effect, and then use the back bed fabric.
Make a hole in the two rows here
Make a hole in the upper row
Then simulate
This is the back effect
Click on the application
This is the organization effect like a grid hole structure
Click on the application and close
In our main variable
You can also adjust the number of rows per inch
And the number of rows per inch
Can be implemented in the 3D window
Adjust
Then we will adjust its color
Set it to red
Now we can create another layer
Next we make a hole in the chest
Include a border without a gap in its front
And used the hole effect
Select this template
Apply
And then choose this here
Then select the wool product and select the needle.
The horizontal line number is set to 8.
The horizontal line number is also 8.
The line thickness is kept at 1.
The density of the line circle is a little bigger here, which is 3.5.
A little smaller.
Then you want it to have this kind of dilution effect.
This tool is called the back needle.
And then I'm going to make some holes for it here.
Then simulate it.
Click on the application.
Also modify its color.
This one will be a little more diluted.
It has a kind of hollow effect.
Then we use the seamless division tool.
It's a curve like this.
We press the Ctrl key above to draw a curve.
It's the same as drawing an internal line.
Then use the internal adjustment.
Adjust the curve point tool.
Adjust its curvature.
Okay.
Then let's adjust its curve line.
After adjusting it almost,
we apply it to the structure of the chest hollow.
Let's simulate it again.
And then the middle panel is still made of large fabric.
Now let's divide the shoulder.
Make the body.
A roof line center.
All right.
Then the main part is the arm.
Press Ctrl key.
Then press Ctrl key.
For this,
we will have to open the Min as well.
Press Ctrl key to open it.
Now we can see the main part.
And then we can see the upper part.
So there is a pretty big gap.
In this way,
We can see that the upper part is completely filled.
And then we can see the lower place.
So we'll have to make it a little bit bigger.
然后它的后片跟前片是一样的。
这边也是做一个无缝分区,也是做一个无缝分区线。
调一下它的弧线。
把这个镂空面料应用上去。
好,接下来呢,我们再来做这个袖口。
那这个袖口呢,我们同样也是使用这个无缝分区。
画一条无缝分区线。
双击结束。
给它应用上去。
选择毛织产品。
选择平针。
然后把它的颜色改成红色。
然后我们再来输入它的纵向悬线数量和横向悬线数量。
这边一个是8,一个是5。
纱线粗心呢,我们来设置的粗一点。
这边是一个5。
悬线密度设置的2。
这边呢,我们可以自定义一下它的每英寸纵行数。
输入的是2.5。
每英寸横列数呢是3.2。
面量厚度输入一个8.8。
然后我们来重置一下织片。
然后也可以让它更厚一点点。
因为袖口想让它更饱满一些。
那现在呢是直接使用这个反针。
然后每两列去给它做一个反针。
模拟一下。
然后点击应用。
这样就是有一个粗棒针的一个效果。
接下来我们来做领子。
那以及把袖子的装饰条也应用上去。
那也是相同的步骤啊。
领子这边的数据呢,一个是4。
横向数量也是4。
纱线粗细是1.5。
线线密度是7。
然后这边就做一个简单的一个反针。
点击应用。
设置一下颜色。
接下来呢我们再来做这个袖子的装饰条。
这个就是做一个很疏松的一个针织效果啊。
纵向线圈数量设置一个6。
横向的呢也是一个6。
先来重置一下。
那这边呢我们设置的粗一点也是5。
线线密度设置的小一点是1.5。
这边使用前身床不编织去做一些大的镂空效果。
再用这个反针去在中间去做一些反针效果。
然后模拟一下。
点击应用并关闭。
这样就是有一个比较大的粗棒针了。
这就是我们的一个镂空效果了。
设置一下颜色。
然后我们再来做一下这个胸部和绑带的装饰条的一些面料的应用。
然后在我们的图库窗口中呢,
我们可以找一个丝绒面料,
可以用于这个前胸口的一个面料中。
先看一下它这个现在用的是什么面料。
这两个用的是同一块面料。
那么我们先给它用丝绒面料覆盖上去。
然后呢,在我们图库窗口中,
有给大家一个绑带的这个蝴蝶结面料。
我们选择这几个板片,
然后又用这块面料。
然后选择这个丝绒面料,
改一下颜色为红色。
然后再选择这个面料。
我们模拟一下,
让它们应用各自的物理属性。
我们这个款式呢,
制作完成了。
我们先来保存一下,
暂时先不提高服装品质,
因为等一下我们需要做一个整装的搭配。
点击新项目。
我们现在呢,
就开始来制作这个半裙了。
导入我们的这个模特文件。
我们来制作这一款半裙。
点击2D。
点击版片生成器。
那在我们的版片生成器这里呢,
我们的新版本是有新增了两个款式,
一个是裤子,
一个是半裙。
然后呢,
这一期呢,
我们是来主要做半裙。
那在这里呢,
我们是可以选择两种不同的半裙的。
那这款呢,
是圆形半裙。
我们可以在下方去输入不同的数值,
来生成对应的版片。
以及在后方可以看到,
我们有一个AI版片生成器。
点击它,
我们可以通过提示词生成以及图片生成。
比如说,
提示词生成也是需要选择它的类型,
以及它的款式。
那在关键词提示这边,
我们来试一下它的随机生成。
点击开始生成。
这是一个大裙摆的散裙,
然后再次点击开始生成。
现在我们的版片呢,
就生成出来了。
那款式基本上是跟我们的这个线稿图很像的,
都是一个很大的一个散摆群。
那如果有对它有细微的调整的话,
那可以在左侧去进行输入。
然后我们再来看一下这个图片生成。
那同样也是要选择它的类型和款式。
然后我来上传一个成品的一个服装图像。
点击开始生成。
可以看到,
那这个版片呢就已经生成出来了。
那同样也是可以在左侧对数据进行调整。
好,现在呢,
我们将它改回这个圆形半裙。
在次量值这边,
我们有三个选项可以进行选择。
现在我们就用这个常规选项就可以了。
那在前裙片这边呢,
可以看到它可以选择对称或者是左右对称。
以及可以选择需不需要带有嗓道。
现在呢我们来调整一下它的腰围。
那我希望我的这个裙子的腰围呢,
一圈是550。
那我现在输入一半的腰围,
那就是275。
那同样也可以选择后方的一个总长。
那这样的话,
它会自动的帮我们乘乘以2。
然后我们,
我现在再反选,
然后再次输入275。
这样的话,
我们后裙片也要再输入一个275。
然后我们再来调整一下这边。
然后我们再来调整一下它的一个侧缝长。
如果是曲线的话,
那就是现在黄色高亮的一个位置。
那现在我给它改成直线。
那这个呢其实就是我们的一个裙长。
我这边呢来输入一个360。
它是一个很短的一个小裙子。
现在有一些变形。
然后我们在后裙片这边也输入相同的数值。
也是360。
然后我们再来输一下下摆裙摆的一个直线长。
那这个直线长呢,
我希望它的裙摆一半呢是500毫米。
那总长就是1000毫米。
那这边如果我点击总长的话,
也可以输入1000。
然后我们再来调整一下后边的一个桑。
将它这个桑改成1。
然后将它改成距离后中是85毫米。
然后从这里我们来输入膝盖。
接着改这个腰头的一个宽度。
刚刚说了我希望这个腰头的腰围总长是550,
所以我这边输入550。
After the overall data is entered, we can click Save.
We can save this group of data for our next use.
We can also open it here to find our data and import it for use.
Then we click Create and then left-click.
We can create this board.
Now the board will automatically be placed on the model and there will be a sewing line.
Now we draw a circle on the model.
We draw a circle on the model.
Then we can set it to a semi-transparent surface and paste it on the model.
Let's simulate.
Paste the waist on the model.
Let's take a look at the skirt.
First of all, the skirt has a double layer structure, so we need to make it a double layer.
Then the bottom is made of a lotus leaf border, and there is a layer of lace inside.
And then this pocket.
Select these two panels, and then we copy and paste.
Pull it up, and then leave a distance from the inner panel.
Let's sew its waist position.
Let's simulate it.
Then let's make it a little shorter.
Use the panel to expand the outline, and then choose to shrink it.
Shrink it by 30 mm and click OK.
Here it is.
Then let's show again.
Next we use this inner curve tool.
On this outer panel,
Draw a curve with a width of 103 and a height of 53.
Then we can make it a little shorter.
This is our pocket, the position of the cover of the pocket.
Then we use the generate round-shape curve tool to push it in and push out the corners on both sides.
This side is 23 mm, right-click 23, click OK.
On this line, right-click to select the column as the board, the board and the sewing line, and then right-click to add it to the outside, and simulate it.
Delete these extra sewing lines at the bottom, and then simulate it.
Ctrl D to duplicate the symmetry, simulate.
Then we draw this inner line, right-click to select the inner line border, the border is 5, click OK.
After drawing this inner line, we will make a column layer, select the outer side of the column layer, and then simulate it.
Then we make the cross-sectional group now.
In the inner line border here, enter a 140, the back piece is the same.
Then select these two lines, select cut and sew, and put it down first.
After we select this group, pull it long, right-click.
Then we select this group, pull it long, right-click, and then select this group, pull it long, right-click.
The column is at a length of 800, and the back piece is the same.
We can freeze the clothes except these two tiles.
模拟一下,拉拽一下这个裙摆,解冻,再来模拟一下。
然后我们再做一个克隆层外部,这个是双层的一个裙摆。
删除掉多余的缝纫线,然后我们再来重新对它进行缝纫。
然后我们再来重新对它进行缝纫。
将它们俩进行重新缝纫。
然后我们解除一下连动。
把这两个板片呢,去让它,给它板片外线扩张一下。
往外延伸一个20毫米,点击确认。
这边也是一样的。
这样子我们就完成了。
我们的这个蕾丝的板片呢,会更加的有层次。
里边的板片就出来了两公分。
好,现在呢,我们打开我们的素材。
文件夹,将这个需要的面料拖入进来。
应用所需的面料。
这个是使用格子面料。
这个口袋呢,是使用这个米色的面料。
内侧使用米色面料。
后面是格子面料。
然后中间这一层是使用蕾丝面料。
然后选择它应用上去。
然后我们将这个两个桑道,还有侧缝都缝一下。
都记得修改为叠缝。
现在我们来模拟一下。
然后去给腰带应用一个面料。
将它的物理属性改成松紧带。
我们把这个扣子素材添加进来。
给这个口袋盖呢,一边去增加一个新型的扭扣。
那这个素材呢,也是分享给大家了。
把这个扣子呢,基本是完成了。
我们现在再来处理一下细节。
去给这个腰头去增加一个厚度。
然后我们再来处理一下这个裙子。
这个裙子呢,基本是完成了。
我们现在再来处理一下细节。
去给这个腰头去增加一个厚度。
再加一个渲染厚度。
这边输入一个1.5。
然后呢,我们再来给这个裙摆添加贴边。
双击结束。
添加完贴边。
然后我们。
再来添加外面这一层的面料的贴边。
来模拟一下。
这里稍微拉拽一下。
这边补一下它的缝纫线。
调整一下它的这个板片的一个外轮廓。
把它的这边调得圆顺一点。
另外一边也是一样的。
给它都拉成直的,会更加的顺一点。
好。
最后来模拟调整一下。
这个款式呢,我们来保存一下。
先另存为一个项目。
另存为一个项目。
然后我们将这个上衣文件给它增加进来。
不要虚拟模特,点击确认。
不要虚拟模特点击确认不要虚拟模特点击确认
好
增加进来之后我们调整一下2D版片的一个位置
现在呢它是有一点点穿透的
我们先给它总体的存一下哦
那我们在调整穿搭这个服装的时候呢
先把这个蝴蝶结细小的版片给它反激活一下
然后呢将这个裙子冷冻主将层设置为-1
再来模拟一下
那这个裙子
这个裙子
就穿到了这个毛衣里面
如果大家在制作的时候模拟的速度很慢
那就可以将这个毛织产品的显示给它先关闭
这样模拟速度会更快一点
然后现在我们将蝴蝶结激活
然后再来调整一下它穿透的位置将它往外拉一点点
另外半边先反激活先激活
激活另外一边
另一边呢就直接给它应用对称就好了
然后我们给它换一下发型增加一个配饰
然后这边呢还给大家提供了一个袜子然后呢还给大家提供了一个袜子
增加进来
点击确认
以及围巾也是增加进来
制作一个整体圣诞风格的穿搭
然后我们将这个头发改成一个深棕色的一个头发
点击确认
然后也是反激活一下这个头发
这边这边有一些穿透啊
所以说我们来调整一下穿透的围巾
然后把这个袜子也是挪一下
先给它冷冻住
然后大补将这个大身板片都给它冻住
然后将毛衣的层设置为服衣
然后让这个围巾
模拟稳定
好
可以手动拉拽一下围巾的形态
全部给它反激活
然后现在呢我们来看一下这个袜子
基本是一个稳定的一个状态
把它的层都改回来
然后这两个板片呢
也是继续给它反激活
把这个袜子的固定针先给它删掉
然后这个袜子呢需要我们去加一下固定的针
fixed on the virtual model on the fixed needle
and then we add a sewing needle to the scarf
fixed on this top
and then look at the overall simulation
and then show the wool product
check the details
and then we can change the posture
when changing the posture, we turn off the display of the wool product
so that the speed will be faster
after changing the posture, let's simulate
to make it more stable
finally, let's improve the quality of the clothing
after improving the quality of the clothing
the sleeve is a little bit flat
because the seam is a little bit loose
the seam is a little bit loose
because the creases might be a little heavy
so we can use the inner line curved tool
here to add an inner line
a closed图形
and then pinch a line
is the shoulder side, choose a thin line
and then simulate again
That way, the sleeve will support it.
And this kind of needle-like clothing, because the different structures of the needle have different thicknesses,
so some of the structure of the needle will have some penetrations with the clothing after improving the quality.
So we will increase the thickness of the needle structure of the sleeve.
Then we will modify it again.
There was a little penetrance in the front chest.
After the modification, the penetrations on this side have improved.
Then we will modify it again.
Now let's see its effect.
You can see that after the penetrations are completed,
the structure of the needle can be displayed more beautifully.
That's all for today's live broadcast.
Thank you for watching.